(upbeat instrumental music)
♪ It's my party and
I'll cry if I want to ♪
♪ Cry if I want to ♪
♪ You would cry too if
it happened to you ♪
♪ Well, now nobody knows
where my Johnny has gone ♪
♪ Johnny has gone ♪
♪ But Judy left the same time ♪
♪ Why was he holding her hand ♪
♪ When he's supposed
to be mine ♪
♪ It's my party and
I'll cry if I want to ♪
♪ Cry if I want to ♪
♪ You would cry too if
it happened to you ♪
♪ Judy and Johnny just
walked through the door ♪
♪ Like a queen with her king ♪
♪ Oh, what a birthday surprise ♪
♪ Judy's wearing his ring ♪
♪ It's my party and
I'll cry if I want to ♪
♪ Cry if I want to ♪
♪ You would cry too if
it happened to you ♪
(slow instrumental music)
♪ She don't know that
she's a lucky girl ♪
♪ Got the best thing in
the whole wide world ♪
♪ Got a love that's
hard to find ♪
♪ She's got the boy
I wish were mine ♪
♪ But she's a fool ♪
♪ She's a fool ♪
♪ She has his love
but treats him cruel ♪
♪ I know there is
gonna come a day ♪
♪ He will tell her,
girl be on your way ♪
♪ Maybe then he'll turn to me ♪
♪ Then oh how happy I will be ♪
♪ That she's a fool ♪
♪ Oh, she's a fool ♪
♪ She has his love
but treats him cruel ♪
♪ She's a fool ♪
♪ Oh ♪
(audience clapping)